### Dawn- Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre, Princes Town.

Tel: (868) 469-6292/373-7306. Email: dmarthamc@outlook.com

6<sup>th</sup> June, 2016

To Whom It May Concern.

Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am applying for positions in **Customer Service** that may be available within the organization.

Given the opportunity, I will not hesitate to demonstrate a keen sense of responsibility, diligence and commitment to duty. I consider myself to be a critical thinker with a drive to see tasks completed till the end. I strongly believe that the training and experiences I have had thus far, brings a balance needed in the type of environment we live and work in today.

I will be pursuing my studies in Business Management in the near future, thus increasing the quality of my capabilities on the job and bringing me closer to my aim of effectively managing my own business full time someday. In the meantime, I view every working and volunteering opportunity as a learning tool used in my development by challenging myself to become the best steward over the responsibilities assigned to me. Additionally, I am always willing to learn to be more effective in such. It is not always easy, but that's where I believe growth comes.

These experiences have taught me the importance of building strong and respectable work relationships with staff and clients. In doing so, I have seen where the clientele and productivity of staff have both increased.

In closing, I do look forward to an interview with you at your convenience and hope that you view me as a suitable candidate for hire.

Thanking you in advance.

Yours respectfully,	
Mrs. Dawn McLeod. (Applicant)	

### Curriculum Vitae

### Dawn-Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre, Princes Town.

Contact: (868) 469-6292 Email: <a href="mailto:dmarthamc@outlook.com">dmarthamc@outlook.com</a>

## Work Experience

July 2015- Current

Revival Fire

**Administrative Assistant (Voluntary)** 

**Contact:** 225-7286/726-5601

**Duties:** General Administrative Duties.

**Feb. 2014 – Current.** 

TFRS Tiling Fabricating and Renovation Services.

Partner

**Contact:** 356-5549

**Duties:** General Administrative and Customer Service Duties.

Dec. 2013 - Feb. 2014

LSC Tutoring

(Worked From Home)

**Service Coordinator** 

Contact: 330-8341

Duties: Plan and Coordinate organization's events and workshops, Customer Service,

Timesheets and Payroll, Basic Graphic Designs for flyers etc. and Marketing.

#### 2010 and 2012

Daniel Johnson Scaffolding

Point Fortin

Administrative Assistant

Contact: 722-0329/ 334-1054

**Duties:** General administrative duties, Time sheets and Payroll including Banking Duties, Supervise workers, Customer Service, Errands for Executives, Receptionist Duties etc.

#### 2011

Youth for Christ

Barataria

**Technical/ Graphic Assistant (Studio)** 

Contact: 674-3931

## Work Experience Continued.

#### 2010

Anthony Henry and Associates Co. Ltd.

Chaguanas

**Human Resource Coordinator** 

Contact: 733-0038

**Duties:** Assist Executives in the hiring and firing process based on the Human Resource regulations of the organization governed by Law, Timesheets, Payroll, Develop Policies and Procedures for company, Report writing, Performance Appraisals, Errands, Motivational Incentives etc.

### 2006-2009

2000-2001

Various Entry Level Jobs (Cashier, Receptionist, Voluntary services, etc.)

# **Qualifications**

2010- 2013	Advanced Christian Training Seminars  Certificate in Ministry
2007	School of Business and Computer Science (SBCS)  Certificate (Introductory) Human Resource Management
2003-2004	Youth Training and Employment Partnership Program Certificate Level 1 Hairdressing

Junior Achievement of Trinidad and Tobago

**Education** 

**Junior Achiever** 

2006	Private Candidate	<b>General Proficiency</b>		
Human and Social Biology		Grade III	(3)	
2003-2004	Private Candidate			
Mathematics		Grade III	(3)	
2002-2003	Bishops' Centenary College			
English A		Grade II	(2)	
Food & Nutrition		Grade II	(2)	
Social-Studies	`	Grade III	(3)	

# **Education Continued**

**1997-2001** Providence Girls RC Secondary School

1995-1997 St. Joseph Girls RC School

# **References**

## Mrs. Marsha R. Pedro

Audit Supervisor Unit Trust Corporation #26 Southern Main Road. Couva.

Contact: 625-8648

## Mr. Kyron C. Regis

Administrator Revival Fire #73 Southern Main Road Marabella.

Contact: 225-7286/726-5601